GUIDE TO THE AMERICAN ASSOCIATION OF SCHOOL ADMINISTRATORS COLLECTION MS2352
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
American Association of School Administrators Collection
1857-2016
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
American Association of School Administrators
MS2352
121 Linear Feet
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of the American Association of School Administrators, 2016.
Arrangement
Organized into 8 series, arranged by series title.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research. Some files are restricted. Files flagged as restricted are subject to review by Special Collections staff before being made available for research. As researchers request materials, a review of the documents will take place. Staff will remove any documents with social security numbers, employee numbers or other sensitive identifying information. Any document found including this information is closed for 90 years from date of creation, or until verifiable proof of a person's death is given. After these documents are removed the folder will be available for research. In some cases, items may be photocopied and redacted. The redacted copy will then be placed in the publicly available folder. All other materials in a folder will be freely available for immediate use and will be marked as having been reviewed by Special Collections staff. After folders have been reviewed using these procedures and the confidential materials have been removed, the restriction shall be lifted.
Scope and Contents
The collection is arranged into 8 series. The series are: Awards; Constituent Relations/Communications; Governance/Planning; Historic; Library/A-V; Membership; Operations; and Public Policy.
Public Schools; Education -- United States -- History; Education; Education policy; School administrators; Professional Employees; Professional Associations
- Awards, 1958-2008; Series 1; 6 Linear Feet
  Arrangement
  Series is arranged alphanumerically by title, then chronologically within the same title.
  Scope and Contents
  Series consists of awards given by or to the American Association of School Administrators, and records about those awards, including event programs and invitations, nominees and award criteria, applications, photographs and slides, and other paperwork. Box 4 contains a commerative plate, and box 9 contains medals.
  - The 12th Annual Sallie Mae First Class Teacher Award, 1995; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The 15th Annual Salie Mae First Class Teacher Award, undated; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 20th Annual Leadership For Learning Awards & Application, 2001; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The 22nd Annual Leadership For Learning Awards & Application, 2003; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 22nd Annual National School Facilities Workshop, June 1991; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 25 Year Membership Award & Suggestions For 1986 Awards, April 1985; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 32nd Annual Exhibition of School Architecture, February 1981; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 32nd Annual Exhibition of School Architecture, February 1982; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 35th Annual Exhibition of School Architecture, February 1984; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 38th Annual Exhibition of School Architecture, February 1987; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 50th Grand Finale Program, February 1976; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 135th Annual Conference & Exposition, February 2003; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 136th Annual Conference & Exposition, February 2004; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 1966 National Teacher of the Year: Mrs. Mona W. Dayton, Tuscon, Arizona, Series 1 (Box 309, Folder 1)
  - 2003 National Superintendent of the Year Program & Application Packet, 2002-2003; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - About the Awards, 1987; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Addendum to 1991 Convention Program, Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - AIT/AASA Award Winners [1/2], 1996; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - AIT/AASA Award Winners [2/2], 1996; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - AIT/AASA Awards 1996 Nominees, 1995; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - AIT/AASA Correspondence, 1995; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Annual Awards Banquet: Starring Larry Gatlin, 1989; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Annual Awards Dinner & NASE Banquet, February 1987; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Annual Awards Dinner, February 1988; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Awards Conference, 2003; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Annual Exhibition of School Architecture, 1974-1976; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Annual Exhibition of School Architecture, 1978-1979; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Annual Exhibition of School Architecture, 1986-1987; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Annual Exhibition of School Architecture, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Annual Exhibition of School Architecture, 1991, 1993; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Architecture Award Program, 2004; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - The Architectural Exhibit, August 1994; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Associated Exhibitors: Grand Finale Program, 1967-1975; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Awards Book, 2006; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Awards Ceremony, February 2005; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Awards Dinner, 1986-1987; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Awards, Honors, & Residencies, 1980-1992; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Awards Presentation Nitecap, February 1992; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Awards Programs, 1989-1991; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Awards and Recognition Programs, March 1988; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Beatrix Sebastian, C. 1971; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Bernard C. Watson 1967 Scholarship Recepient, 1966; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Burger King Scholarships, 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Business Week Awards [1/2], 1995; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Business Week Awards [2/2], 1995; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Business Week Correspondence, 1995-1996; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - A Celebration of Accomplishments TED/TAC, February 1999; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Challenges/ Changes Slides (Stats 1920-1990's), unknown; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Civic Star Award, 2003; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - The Civic Star Award: National Winners, 2003-2007; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - The Conference Daily, February 2005; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - The Council of Educational Facility Planners International, 1990; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Distinguished Service Awards, 1978-1980; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Distinguished Service Awards, 1981-1983; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Education's Starts of the Year Award, 1984-1986; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Education's Starts of the Year Award, 1984-1989; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Email: Check for 1992 Leadership For Learning Award, July 1992; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Exhibition of School Architecture, 1971-1972; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Exhibition of School Architecture, March 1973; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Exhibition of School Architecture, 1990; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Exhibitin of School Architecture, 1992; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Exhibition of School Architecture, February 1997; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Exhibition of School Architecture, 1997-1999; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Exhibition of School Architecture, February-March 1998; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Exhibition of School Architecture; The National Conference on Education, 2001, 2003; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Exhibition of School Architecture at The National Conference on Education, February 1997; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Exhibition of School Architecture-Requst for Submissions; The National Conference on Education, February 1994; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - First Annual Awards Dinner; Education Stars of the Year, February 1984; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - A First Class Look at Teaching by Marjorie Leppo & Diane Davis, September 1999; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Golden Key Awards, varies; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Grand Finale Program, February 1972; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - leadership in Changing Times, July 2002; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Leadership Conference, May 1992; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Leadership Conference, April 1998; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Leadership for Learning Awards & Application, 2002; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - The Leadership for Learning Awards & Winners, 2002; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Leadership for Learning; Portfolio Historical File, 1994-2000; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Legal Support Program, 1990-2001; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Legal Support Program, 1994; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Legal Support Program, unknown; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Loose Documents, 1993,1995; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Memorandum, August 1986; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Memorandum, 1988-1999; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Minuites of Executive Commitee Meeting, April 1965; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - National Conference on Education, February 1995; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - The National Conference on Education, March 1996; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - The National Conference on Education, 1996-1997; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - The National Conference on Education, 2006-2008; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Installation of President Roland "Goldie" Haun Fort Knox, Kentucky, March 12, 1994; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - The National Conference on Educational Daily Vol. XVII No. 2, February 1995; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - National Superintendent of the Year Award and Applicaton, 1998; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - National Superintendent of the Year Award and Application, 1999; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - National Superintendent of the Year Award and Aplication, 2001; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - National Superintendent of the Year Program, 2002; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - National Superintendent of the Year Program, 15th Anniversary, 2002; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - OSBA Capital Conference and Trade Show, November 1990; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Paul B. Memorial Lecture Guidelines, undated; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Philadelphia Utah State Board of Education (USOE) Program, 1981-1983; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Photo File #188, Convention 1985, Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Presidents Award Ceremony and Reception, 1999-2000; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Presidents Award Ceremony and Reception, 1993-2003; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Presidents Award Ceremony and Reception, 1998, 2003; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Presidents Technology Award, undated; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Program and Exhibits, 124th Convention, February 1992; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Program and Exhibits Addendum-The National Confernce on Education, February 1994; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Richard, Viering, 1970; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Sallie Mae Teachers Award Program, 1984-1989; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Sallie Mae Teachers Award Recipients, 1987; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Sallie Mae Teacher Award Recipients, 1988; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Sallie Mae First Year Teacher Award Recipients, 1989; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Sallie Mae Winners List, 1985-1998; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Salute to the Stars, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Samwood Buildings, 1984; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Scholarship Senate Directory, 1996; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Scholarship Senate Directory, 1997; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Scholarship Senate Directory, 1998; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Scholarship Senate Directory, 1999; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Scholarship Senate Directory, 2000; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Scholarship Senate Directory, 2001; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Scholarship Senate Directory, 2002; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Scholarship Senate Directory, 2004; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Scholarship Senate Directory, 2006; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Scholarship Senate Directory, 2008; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Scholarship Senate Directory, 2009; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - The School Administrator Vol. 17 No. 5, January 1960; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - School Architecture, 1977-1978; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - School Architecture, 1980; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - School Buildings AASA Filmstrip Booklets, 1974-1976; Series 1 (Box 316, Folder 1)
  - School Buildings AASA Filmstrip Film Canisters, 1970, 1974-1976; Series 1 (Box 316, Folder 2)
  - School Building Architectural Directory, 1986; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - School Buildings, 1985; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - School Buildings: Filmstrip Discussion Manuel, 1971; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - School Buildings: Filmstrip Discussion Manual, 1972; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - School Buildings Filmstrip, 1974; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - School Buildings Filmstrip, 1975; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - School Buildings Invoices, 1983; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - School Building Invoices, 1984; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - School Building Slides, 1977; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - School Building Slide Collection, 1987; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - School Buildings Slides and Pamphlet, 1977; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - School Buildings Slides and Pamphlet, 1978; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - School Buildings Slides and Pamphlet, 1980; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - School Buildings Slides and Pamphlet, 1981; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - School Buildings Slides and Pamphlet, 1982; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - School Buildings Slides and Pamphlet, 1984; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - School Building Slides and Various Slides, 1984, 1998; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Seager, Roger C., C. 1958; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Second Annual Awards Dinner: Education's Stars of the Year, March 1985; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Seventeen Annual Banquet and Distringuished Lecture, February 1986; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Seventeen Annual Leadership for Learning Awards, 1997; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - The Shifting Educational Landscape: Advocating for Student Success, 2013; Series 1 (Box 316, Folder 3)
  - Shirley Cooper and Walter Taylor Architectural Award Winners, 1973-2002; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Small School District Administrator's Conference: 34th Annual School Architectural Awards, June 1983; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Special Awards Night Programs, 1979-1980; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Special Awards Night Program, 1981, 1984-1985; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Spencer, Ralph L., C. 1961; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - State Association Executives: Awards and Recognition Handbook, 1997; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Taylor, Jack P., 1963; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Testing Where We Stand, 1989; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Third Annual Awards Dinner Featuring O.J. Simpson, February 1986; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Thirty Second Annual Program Series: Associated Exhibitors of the National Education Association, 1958; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Tips For Moderators, undated; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Various Title Slides, undated; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Superintendent of the Year Award Box, 1994; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Superintendent of the Year Award, 1992; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Superintendent of the Year Award, 2000; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Superintendent of the Year Award, 1996; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Superintendent of the Year Award, 1998; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Superintendent of the Year Award, 2002; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Superintendent of the Year Award-Silver, 1990; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Superintendent of the Year Award-Bronze, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Superintendent of the Year Award, 2002; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Superintendent of the Year Award, 1993; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Superintendent of the Year Award, 1998; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Superintendent of the Year Award, 1995; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Superintendent of the Year Award, 2001; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Constituent Relations/ Communications, 1943-2016; Series 2; 12 Linear Feet
  Series is arranged alphabetically by title, then chronologically for shared titles.
  Series primarily contains materials published by the AASA to communicate with members. This includes magazines-especially the School Administrator as it evolved into a modern, glossy publication-as well as audio and video material. In particular, the videos contain interviews and messages from former AASA director Dr. Paul Houston.
  - The AASA Professor Vol. 26 No.3, 2004; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Article in Education Week, June, 1990; Series 2 (Box 249, Folder 16)
  - Blueline [Intelligble] [1/2], 1979-1983; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Blueline [Intelligble] [2/2], 1979-1983; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Cover [1/2], 1982-1984; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Cover [2/2], 1982-1984; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Cover and Spot Illustration Assignments/PO's, 1956, 1959-1960, 1984-1985; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Conference Daily Newspapers, 1995; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Conference Daily Newspapers, 1996; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Conference Daily Newspapers, 1997; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Conference Daily Newspapers, 1998; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Conference Daily Newspapers, 1999; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Conference Daily Newspapers, 2000; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Conference Daily Newspapers, 2001; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Conference Daily Newspapers, 2002; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Conference Daily Newspapers, 2003; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Conference Daily Newspapers, 2004; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Conference Daily Newspapers, 2005; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Conference Daily Newspapers, 2006; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Conference Daily Newspapers, 2008; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Conventioneer, 1986; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Conventioneer, 1988; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Conventioneer, 1990; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Conventioneer, 1991; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Conventioneer, 1992; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Conventioneer, 1993; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Conventioneer, 1994; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - First Pages-Operations Update [1/2], 1979-1981; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - First Pages-Operations Update [2/2], 1979-1981; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Journal of Scholarship and Practice, 2004-2005; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Leadership News Newspaper, 1987; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Leadership News Newspaper, 1988; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Leadership News Newspapers, 1989; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Leadership News Newspapers, 1990; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Leadership News Newspapers, 1991; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Leadership News Newspapers, 1992; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Leadership News Newspapers, 1993; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Leadership News Newspapers, 1994; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Leadership News Newspapers, 1995; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Leadership News Newspapers, 1996; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Leadership News Newspapers, 1997; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Leadership News Newspapers [1/2], 1998; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Leadership News Newspapers [2/2], 1998; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Leadership News Newspapers, 1999; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Partners Program-The School Administrator [1/2], 1957-1965; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Partners Program-The School Administrator [2/2], 1957-1965; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Schneider Feature, What Irks Sopes; The School Administrator, 1976; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - The School Administrator [1/2], 1943-1957; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - The School Administrator [2/2], 1943-1957; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - The School Administrator [1/2], 1965-1969; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - The School Administrator [2/2], 1965-1969; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - The School Administrator, 1968; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - The School Administrator, 1969; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - The School Administrator [1/2], 1969-1971; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - The School Administrator [2/2], 1969-1971; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - The School Administrator, 1970; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - The School Administrator, 1971; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - The School Administrator [1/2], 1971-1973; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - The School Administrator [2/2], 1971-1973; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - The School Administrator, 1972; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - The School Administrator, 1973; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - The School Administrator, 1974; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - The School Administrator, 1975; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - The School Administrator, 1976; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - The School Administrator, 1977; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - The School Administrator, 1978-1979; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - The School Administrator [1/2], 1982; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - The School Administrator [2/2], 1982; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - The School Administrator [1/2], 1983; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - The School Administrator [2/2], 1983; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - The School Administrator [1/2], 1984; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - The School Administrator [2/2], 1984; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - The School Administrator [1/2], 1985; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - The School Administrator [2/2], 1985; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - The School Administrator [1/2], 1986; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - The School Administrator [2/2, 1986; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - The School Administrator [1/2], 1987; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - The School Administrator [2/2], 1987; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - The School Administrator [1/2], 1988; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - The School Administrator [2/2], 1988; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - The School Administrator [1/2], 1989; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - The School Administrator [2/2], 1989; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - The School Administrator [1/2], 1990; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - The School Administrator [2/2], 1990; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - The School Administrator [1/2], 1991; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - The School Administrator [2/2], 1991; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - The School Administrator [1/2], 1992; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - The School Administrator [2/2], 1992; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - The School Administrator [1/2], 1993; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - The School Administrator [2/2], 1993; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - The School Administrator [1/2], 1994; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - The School Administrator [2/2], 1994; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - The School Administrator [1/2], 1995; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - The School Administrator [2/2], 1995; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - The School Administrator [1/2], 1996; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - The School Administrator [2/2], 1996; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - The School Administrator [1/2], 1997; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - The School Administrator [2/2], 1997; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - The School Administrator [1/2], 1998; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - The School Administrator [2/2], 1998; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - The School Administrator [1/2], 1999; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - The School Administrator [2/2], 1999; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - The School Administrator [1/2], 2000; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 1)